《权力的游戏》前情提要
我们已经打赢了生死之战
We have won the Great War.
现在我们要赢下最后一战
Now we will win the last war.
我们的目标是在不摧毁君临的前提下
The objective here is to remove Cersei
除掉瑟曦
without destroying King's Landing.
你打算去君临？
You heading to King's Landing?
我还有些事没有做了断
There's some unfinished business.
我也是
Me too.
我没准备回来
I don't plan on coming back.
我也是
Neither do I.
我一直希望着能亲眼目睹他们处决你姐姐
I always wanted to be there when they execute your sister.
看来我没这个机会了
Seems like I won't get the chance.
留在我身边
Stay with me.
求你了
Please.
瑟曦面目可憎
Cersei's hateful...
我又何尝不是
And so am I.
我要告诉你们一件事
I need to tell you something.
但是你们得发誓不会告诉任何人
But you have to swear you'll never tell another soul.
如果还有其他人呢？其他更好的人选？
What if there's someone else? Someone better.
在某个时刻 你会选择一个你信赖的人
At a certain point, you choose a person you believe in,
为那人战斗
and you fight for that person.
即便你知道这是个错误的选择？
Even if you know it's a mistake?
他的继承顺位更靠前
He has the better claim to the throne.
每个坦格利安诞生之时
Every time a Targaryen is born,
诸神都会抛一枚硬币
the gods flip a coin.
疯王处决了他的敌人
The Mad King gave his enemies the justice
他认为他们罪有应得
he thought they deserved.
子女和父辈并不一样
Children are not their fathers.
- 成为一条巨龙吧  - 您有颗仁慈的心
- Be a dragon. - You have a gentle heart.
一个坦格利安族人孤独地活在世上
A Targaryen alone in the world
是件很可悲的事情
is a terrible thing.
你不想唤醒睡龙之怒 对吧？
You don't want to awake the dragon, do you?
m -11 -35 l -11 39 l 63 39 l 63 -35
m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34
最专业冰火字幕
诚意奉献
翻译 季叽馥疾己
翻译 阿尔帕东诺
绝境长城  the Wall
翻译 黄金镖客猫
翻译 熊岛莱安娜
最后壁炉城Last Hearth
翻译 LittleFireAidan
最专业的华语冰火资料站：        冰与火之歌中文维基
https://asoiaf.huijiwiki.com
m 31 -6 l -21 40 l 34 22 m 29 -8 l -3 -12 l -24 40
临冬城Winterfell
校对 玫瑰叔
校对 耗斯特洛夫斯卡娅子
校对 北落师门
后期 依依Eva
监制 北落师门
临冬城的墓窖Crypt of Winterfell
监制 临冬城的狮子
联合出品
史诗图书 | 冰火中文维基 | 黑城堡奇幻微刊
Epic Books         ASOIAF.huijiwiki.com          Heichengbao
君临 King's Landing
特别顾问 屈畅(ccxx)@史诗图书
字幕组发起人 baozhenyuawabi
策划 衣柜军团
史诗图书  正统奇幻的圣殿
红堡Red Keep
灰机GAME  开拓你的世界
根据长篇小说
《冰与火之歌》 改编
原著  乔治·R·R·马丁
权力的游戏
衣柜字幕组
m -18.625 0 l -18.625 0 l 281.25 0 l 281.25 1.125 l -18.625 1.125
m -86 -116 b -89 -117 -89 -117 -95 -119 l -97 -115 l -85 -105 l -116 -102 b -116 -100 -116 -98 -116 -97 l -108 -91 l -96 -91 l -116 -63 l -105 -69 l -96 -47 l -74 -63 l -77 -69 l -91 -63 l -91 -77 l -88 -80 l -66 -49 l -46 -63 l -58 -66 l -66 -74 l -49 -80 l -60 -91 l -74 -83 l -80 -91 l -77 -94 l -46 -94 l -52 -108 l -71 -105 b -69 -107 -67 -110 -66 -113 m -31 -119.875 l -33 -119 b -34 -113 -36 -107 -38 -102 l -46 -97 b -42 -93 -38 -89 -35 -85 l -44 -63 b -41 -64 -38 -65 -35 -66 l -35 -52 l -33 -47 l -27 -55 l -27 -69 l -21 -63 l -21 -69 l -19 -72 l -27 -88 l -21 -94 l -21 -99 l -27 -102 l -27 -102 l -30 -116 m -21 -113 l -21 -105 l -21 -99 l -21 -94 l -19 -85 l -19 -66 l -21 -49 l -19 -47 l -7 -52 l 26 -52 l 18 -66 l -7 -63 l -5 -69 l 6 -69 l 18 -69 l 20 -99 l -7 -94 l -7 -83 l 6 -85 l 6 -80 l -7 -77 l -7 -94 l -10 -99 l 23 -102 l 18 -116 l -10 -110 l -19 -116 m -105 -38 l -116 -41 l -110 -13 l -102 -19 l -102 -30 l -63 -33 l -55 -19 l -46 -41 l -49 -44 m -88 -33 l -91 -24 l -99 -24 l -105 -16 l -102 -13 l -85 -16 l -85 -10 l -94 -8 l -85 -16 l -102 -13 l -108 1 l -88 1 l -88 4 l -116 6 l -116 9 l -110 15 l -88 15 l -85 26 l -77 23 l -74 15 l -52 15 l -49 15 l -52 4 l -74 6 l -71 1 l -55 -2 l -60 -13 l -74 -10 l -74 -13 l -55 -16 l -63 -24 l -74 -24 l -80 -33 m -46 -41 l -38 -2 l -41 23 l -38 26 l 1 20 l 15 26 l 18 23 l 18 -8 l 20 -41 l 20 -44 l -24 -38 l -35 -41 l -35 -30 l -13 -30 l -19 -21 l -33 -19 l -33 -13 l -21 -13 l -33 6 l -33 15 l -13 -5 l -13 1 l -21 6 l -13 12 l -2 9 l -2 -8 l 9 -10 l 12 -19 l 1 -21 l -2 -27 l 9 -33 l 6 -16 l 6 -10 l 9 12 l -2 9 l -30 12 l -30 12 l -27 -2 l -27 -2 l -30 -16 l -27 -21 l -35 -41 m -126 -127 l -130 -130 l -129 38 l 34 37 l 35 -135 l -130 -131 l -127 -127 l 30 -129 l 31 32 l -124 34
协力制作
史诗图书
Epic Books
ASOIAF.huijiwiki.com
冰火中文维基
黑城堡
EPICASTLE
第五集
钟
The  Bells
本字幕的制作目的是为了相关爱好者交流学习之用，
请在下载24小时之内删除。请勿用于任何商业用途。
……不是唯一活着的坦格利安传人。雷加和莱安娜……
……他们的儿子还活着，被艾德·史塔克秘密保护。他的名字是……
……他是铁王座的正统继承人。
瓦里斯
“八爪蜘蛛”
请进
Come in.
说呀？
And?
没效果么？
Nothing?
她没吃
She won't eat.
我们晚餐时再试试吧
We'll try again at supper.
我觉得他们在盯着我
I think they're watching me.
- 谁？ - 她的士兵
- Who? - Her soldiers.
当然了 那是他们的职责
Of course they are. That's their job.
玛莎 我和你说过什么来着
What have I told you, Martha?
风险越大 回报越大
The greater the risk, the greater the reward.
去吧 厨房那边找不到你会起疑的
Go on. They'll be missing you in the kitchen.
提利昂·兰尼斯特
“小恶魔” 丹妮莉丝的女王之手
北境军队呢？
The Northern armies?
刚刚渡过三叉戟河
Just crossed the Trident.
他们大概两天后到达君临城外
They'll be at the walls of King's Landing in two days.
她情况如何？
How is she?
自打我们回来之后她就没见过任何人
She hasn't seen anyone since we returned.
房门不出 水米未进
Hasn't left her chambers, hasn't accepted any food.
她不该一个人呆着
She shouldn't be alone.
你为她担忧 我敬佩你的怜悯之心
You're worried for her. I admire your empathy.
你难道不担心么？
Aren't you worried for her?
我担心的是我们所有人
I'm worried for all of us.
人们常说每个坦格利安诞生之时
They say every time a Targaryen is born,
诸神就会抛一枚硬币 而整个世界都会屏息以待
the gods toss a coin and the world holds its breath.
我们北方人可不爱玩猜谜
We're not much for riddles where I'm from.
你我都明白她会采取什么行动
We both know what she's about to do.
琼恩·雪诺
伊耿·坦格利安 铁王座法理继承人
那是她该做的决定 她是我们的女王
That's her decision to make. She is our queen.
权力取决于人心 不管人们是否意识到这一点
Men decide where power resides, whether or not they know it.
你到底想要什么？
What do you want?
我想要的从未改变过
All I've ever wanted.
让一个真正合适的统治者坐上铁王座
The right ruler on the Iron Throne.
她那枚硬币会哪面朝上我不得而知
I still don't know how her coin has landed.
但你那枚我已经很清楚了
But I'm quite certain about yours.
我不想要这个王位
I don't want it.
从没想过
I never have.
我见识过的国王和女王比这世上任何人都要多
I have known more kings and queens than any man living.
我听过他们对老百姓说的好话
I've heard what they say to crowds,
也见过他们背地里干的勾当
and seen what they do in the shadows.
我也曾帮助他们实现计划 无论那有多可怕
I have furthered their designs, however horrible.
但现在我对你说的句句属实
But what I tell you now is true:
你可以做到政治清明 而她——
You will rule wisely and well, while she--
她是……
She...
我的女王
is my queen.
陛下
Your Grace?
有件事需要禀报您
There's something you need to know.
丹妮莉丝·坦格利安
“风暴降生”“龙之母”
有人背叛了我
Someone has betrayed me.
是的
Yes.
琼恩·雪诺
Jon Snow.
瓦里斯
Varys.
他知道了琼恩的真实出身
He knows the truth about Jon.
是的
He does.
因为你告诉了他
Because you told him.
珊莎透露给你
You learned from Sansa.
而她又是从琼恩口中得知的
And she learned from Jon,
尽管我求过他不要告诉珊莎
though I begged him not to tell her.
所以我说……
As I said...
他背叛了我
he betrayed me.
我很庆幸珊莎告知了我
I'm glad Sansa told me.
我是您的首相啊
I am your Hand.
您所要面对的所有威胁我都应该知晓
I need to be aware of any threats you're facing.
那瓦里斯呢？
And Varys?
您的情报总管也应当知晓
Your Master of Whisperers needs to be aware too.
但你先告诉了他
You spoke to him first.
没有提前向我请示
Without coming to me.
没有经过我的允许
Without asking my permission.
这是我的失误
It was a mistake.
你以为珊莎为什么要透露给你？
Why do you think Sansa told you?
你以为她想得到什么结果？
What do you think she hoped to gain?
- 她信任我  - 她当然信任你
- She trusts me. - Yes, she trusts you.
她相信你一定会把秘密传播出去
She trusted you to spread secrets
这个秘密足以毁了你的女王
that could destroy your own queen.
你显然没让她失望
And you did not let her down.
我的女王 如果我辜负了您 原谅我
If I have failed you, my queen, forgive me.
但我们是出于好意
Our intentions were good.
我们的目标和您一致 那就是创造一个更美好的世界
We wanted what you want. A better world, all of us.
瓦里斯也是如此
Varys as much as anyone.
但现在这都不重要了
But it doesn't matter now.
没错
No.
现在不重要了
It doesn't matter now.
灰虫子
无垢者指挥官
是我告发的
It was me.
我希望这是我罪有应得
I hope I deserve this.
真的
Truly, I do.
我希望是我错了
I hope I'm wrong.
再见了 老朋友
Goodbye, old friend.
瓦里斯大人
Lord Varys.
我 坦格利安家族的
I, Daenerys of House Targaryen,
丹妮莉丝一世
First of My Name,
打碎镣铐之人 龙之母
Breaker of Chains and Mother of Dragons...
宣判你死刑
sentence you to die.
卓耿
丹妮莉丝的黑龙
龙焰
Dracarys.
这是我们跨过狭海时
This was all she brought with her
她带来的全部东西
when we crossed the Narrow Sea.
她唯一的财产
Her only possession.
没事的 灰虫子
让我跟他说几句话
我说过如果你告诉你妹妹 会发生什么来着？
What did I say would happen if you told your sister?
我不想要铁王座 我告诉过瓦里斯了
I don't want it, and that's what I told him.
你妹妹背叛了你的信任
She betrayed your trust.
瓦里斯的死 她也有责任
She killed Varys as much as I did.
这对她来说是一场胜利
This was a victory for her.
现在她明白
Now she knows what happens
当人们知道你的身世后 会发生什么了
when people hear the truth about you.
维斯特洛的人民爱你远胜过我
Far more people in Westeros love you than love me.
这里没人爱戴我
I don't have love here.
他们只是怕我
I only have fear.
你有我啊
I love you.
你永远都是我的女王
And you will always be my queen.
我对你而言只是如此吗？
Is that all I am to you?
仅仅是你的女王？
Your queen?
好吧
All right, then.
那就怕下去吧
Let it be fear.
生活在这里的百姓不是你的敌人
The people who live there, they're not your enemies.
他们是无辜的 就像你在弥林解放的那些奴隶一样
They're innocents, like the ones you liberated in Meereen.
在我到弥林的时候
In Meereen, the slaves turned on the masters
奴隶们就已经奋起反抗并且解放了城市
and liberated the city themselves the moment I arrived.
但君临百姓还在害怕
They're afraid.
任何反抗瑟曦的人
Anyone who resists Cersei
他的家族都会被株连
will see his family butchered.
你不能指望他们充英雄
You can't expect them to be heroes.
- 他们是人质 - 是啊
- They're hostages. - They are.
他们被暴君挟持是谁的错？是我的错吗？
In a tyrant's grip. Whose fault is that? Mine?
是谁的错又有什么关系呢？
What does it matter whose fault it is?
如果城市被焚毁 成千上万的孩子都会死去
Thousands of children will die if the city burns.
你姐姐很清楚
Your sister knows how to use
如何利用敌人的弱点去对抗他们
her enemies' weaknesses against them.
她认为我们的仁慈就是
That's what she thinks our mercy is:
我们的弱点
weakness.
- 我恳求您 我的女王 - 但是她错了
- I beg you, my queen - But she's wrong.
仁慈是我们的优势
Mercy is our strength.
但我们的仁慈是留给后世百姓的
Our mercy towards future generations
他们将永远不会再被暴君挟持为人质
who will never again be held hostage by a tyrant.
召集无垢者
Ready the Unsullied.
今晚你们就乘船前往君临
Tonight you sail for King's Landing
- 加入北境大军 - 如果瑟曦的追随者们
- to join the Northern armies. - Cersei's followers
知道这一仗赢不了的话 他们会抛弃她的
will abandon her if they know the war is lost.
给他们这个机会
Give them that chance.
如果他们投降了
If the city surrenders,
他们会鸣钟并且打开城门
they will ring the bells and raise the gates.
如果您听到了钟声 求您下令停止进攻
Please, if you hear them ringing the bells, call off the attack.
在城外等着我
Wait for me outside the city.
到时候你会知道怎么办的
You'll know when it's time.
你哥哥想要穿越防线 被我们抓住了
Your brother was stopped trying to get past our lines.
看来他到最后也没有抛弃你的姐姐
It seems he hasn't abandoned your sister after all.
下一次你再辜负我对你的信任……
The next time you fail me...
我就不会再给你机会了
will be the last time you fail me.
让他们过去
Let them pass.
穿过大门
Through the gate.
后卫部队天亮前应该就会到达
The rearguard should be here by daybreak.
她想要现在就攻城
She wants to attack now.
戴佛斯·席渥斯
“洋葱骑士”
最早也得等到天亮
Daybreak at the earliest.
戴佛斯
Davos.
你得帮我个忙
I need to ask you a favor.
你是这世上最牛逼的走私犯 对吧？
You're the greatest smuggler alive, aren't you?
这个忙不太好帮是么？
I'm not gonna like this favor, am I?
等下 你们要去哪里？
Ay up. Where you going?
桑铎·克里冈
“猎狗”
艾莉亚·史塔克
我是艾莉亚·史塔克
I'm Arya Stark.
我要去杀瑟曦女王
I'm going to kill Queen Cersei.
想想看
Think about it.
要是她杀了瑟曦 战争也就结束了
She kills Cersei, the war's over.
围城战不用打了 明天你也许就不至于战死
There won't be a siege.You might not even die tomorrow.
我需要向长官通报
I need to go talk to my captain.
去啊 向他通报
Go ahead, talk to him.
他要去哪？
Where's he going?
我喝吃头骨看守
我想吃头骨看守
我想见……
我们会说通用语
We speak the common tongue.
啊 那就好
Ah. Good.
我想和囚犯单独呆着
I want to be alone with the prisoner.
休息一会吧 明天会很漫长
Get some rest. Tomorrow will be a long day.
我们有令在身 要看守囚犯
We have orders to guard the prisoner.
谁下令的？ 女王吗？
Ordered by whom? The queen herself?
- 不是 - 这样的话
- No. - Well, in that case,
作为女王之手 我可比下这命令的人级别高
as Hand of the Queen, I outrank whomever gave your order.
可能高很多
Probably by quite a lot.
詹姆·兰尼斯特
“弑君者”
他们怎么发现你的？
How did they find you?
你没考虑过把它取下来吗？
Did you consider taking it off?
瑟曦曾叫我 “最蠢的兰尼斯特”
Cersei once called me "the stupidest Lannister."
你要回到她身边 陪她去送死
And you're going back to her, to die with her.
你之前低估她了
You've underestimated her before.
她死定了
She's going to die.
除非你能说服她
Unless you can convince her
让她改变一下作战方针
to change her course of action.
在这儿很难做到
Difficult to do from here.
我哪次动摇过她的想法？
When have I ever been able to convince Cersei of anything?
那就尽量
Try.
就算不为你自己 不为她
If not for yourself, if not for her,
也要为君临城的众多百姓努力
then for every one of the million people in that city,
无论这些人是否无辜
innocent or otherwise.
说实话 我从来没有真正在乎过他们
To be honest, I never really cared much for them.
无论这些人是否无辜
Innocent or otherwise.
有一个无辜者你肯定在乎
You do care for one innocent.
我知道你一定会
I know you do.
瑟曦也会
And so does Cersei.
她现在有理由这么做
She has a reason now.
那个孩子就是她寸步不让的理由
The child is the reason she'll never give an inch.
她做过那么多可怕的事情
All the worst things she's ever done,
都是为了她的孩子
she's done for her children.
她也不是完全不可能打赢
It's not impossible that she'll win.
她不会赢的
She won't.
她的敌人的兵力都已损耗大半
Her enemy's forces have been depleted,
正如她所说的那样
as she said they would be.
三条龙中的两条已经死了
Two of the three dragons are dead.
- 她已经扳回了劣势 - 君临明天一定会陷落
- She's evened the odds. - The city will fall tomorrow.
她有兰尼斯特大军 她有黄金团——
She has the Lannister army, she has the Golden Company--
上次君临遭到攻击时 是我在保卫它
I defended the city last time it was attacked.
我比任何人都清楚 明天它会陷落
I know it better than anyone. It will fall tomorrow.
那看来我要死在明天了 除非我还会死得更早
Then I suppose I'll die tomorrow, if not before.
为什么？
Why?
逃吧
Escape.
你们俩一起
The two of you, together.
记得我们曾经会面的地方吗
Remember where we met,
在红堡地下
where they keep the dragon skulls,
存放龙头骨的地方？
beneath the Red Keep?
把她带到那里去
Take her down there.
沿着楼梯一直往下走
Keep following the stairways down,
走到最深处
down as far as they'll go.
你们就能出来 到红堡脚下的沙滩上
You'll come out onto a beach at the foot of the keep.
那儿会有只小船等着你们
A dinghy will be waiting for you.
划出海湾
Sail out of the bay.
如果风向合适 你们就能划到潘托斯
If the winds are kind, you'll make it to Pentos.
开始新的生活吧
Start a new life.
从铁舰队眼皮底下划船过去 开始新生活？
Sail right past the Iron Fleet and into a new life?
听起来比瑟曦打胜仗更不靠谱
Sounds a lot less likely than Cersei winning this war--
很快那里就不会有什么铁舰队了
There won't be an Iron Fleet for much longer.
去吧
Do it.
如果你不这么做 你永远都见不到瑟曦了
If you don't, you'll never see Cersei again.
对我发誓
Swear to me.
我保证
You have my word.
如果成功了
If it works,
就下令敲响君临所有的钟
give the order to ring all the bells
打开城门
in King's Landing and open the gates.
这会是君临城投降的信号
That will be our signal that the city has surrendered.
我会尽力
I'll try.
我从没想过 我会报答你的帮助
I never thought I'd get to repay the favor.
记住 敲钟 开城门
Remember, ring the bells and open the gates.
你的女王会因此处决你的
Your queen will execute you for this.
如果丹妮莉丝可以不用大开杀戒
If Daenerys can make it to the throne
就登上王位
without wading through a river of blood,
或许她就会仁慈地对待
maybe she'll show mercy
帮她实现这一切的人
to the person who made that possible.
成千上万的无辜百姓......
Tens of thousands of innocent lives...
和一个不是那么无辜的侏儒……
one not particularly innocent dwarf...
这波交易不亏
it seems like a fair trade.
如果不是你
If it weren't for you,
我早就夭折了
I never would've survived my childhood.
才不会
You would have.
你是唯一一个
You were the only one
没有把我当成怪物的人
who didn't treat me like a monster.
你是我的全部
You were all I had.
攸伦·葛雷乔伊
铁群岛之王
注意地平线！
Eyes on the horizon!
蝎弩装弹！
Load the scorpion!
弓箭手 跟上！
Archers, close up!
过来！
Come on!
弹射弩就位！
Up to the espringal!
到它后面去！
To the back of it!
弓箭手 列队！
Archers, line up!
这边！过来！
This way! Come on!
现在清理街道！
Clear the streets now!
- 不！ - 赶快进去！
- No! - In, now.
- 你 过来 - 赶紧回屋！
- And you, come on. - Inside, now!
快点
Quickly.
是的 朝那边走
Yes. Follow down there.
他们来了 到红堡去
They're here. Get to the Red Keep.
- 儿子！ - 进去！
- My son! - Get inside!
就在你前面 我看见了！
Just ahead of you, I can see it!
好吧 行动！
All right, move it!
- 过来！ - 往前走！
- Come on! - Keep moving!
- 往前走！- 继续往前！
- Keep going! - Keep moving!
- 快点！ - 一直往前！
- Quickly! - All the way!
- 过来！ - 过来！
- Come on! - Come on!
抓紧你妈妈的手！
Hold your mother's hand!
给黄金团让路！
Make way for the Golden Company!
关上大门！
Close the gate!
哈利·斯崔克兰
黄金团团长
如果你听到了钟声 就表示他们投降了
If you hear the bells ring, they've surrendered.
让你手下的人停手
Call off your men.
兄弟 向前走
Move along now, lads.
瑟曦·兰尼斯特
铁王座上的女王
- 就这样 - 继续 快走
- That's it. - Go on, move it.
跟上 动起来 走起来 快点 快一点 跟上 快走
Come on, move, move. Faster, faster. Come on, move it.
- 继续走 - 继续向前走
- Keep going. - Keep moving.
- 让开 - 别和他走散了
- Move. - Stay with him.
- 抓好了 - 抓住我的手
- Hold on. - Hold my hand.
跟在这个人后面
Get behind there.
关上大门！
Close the gate!
不准进了
No more through.
- 不要 - 妈妈 不要
- No. - No. Mommy.
- 维姬！求求开门啊！ - 不要啊 求您开门！
- Vicky! Please! - No, please, sir!
- 开门啊！ - 关门！
- Open the gate! - Close the gate!
- 开门！- 开开门啊！
- Open it! - Open the gate!
- 后退 - 听着 去试试那扇门 走 快走
- Get back. - Look, try that one. Go. Go.
大门现在已关闭！
The gates are locked now!
打开！
Open!
- 后退！- 开门啊！
- Get back! - Open the gate!
军爷！军爷！
Soldier! Soldier!
- 求求您开门吧！- 滚回家去！
- Please open the gate! - Go back to your homes!
后退！门已经关上了！
Stay back! It's closed!
当兵的！
Soldier!
让开！别挤！
Move away! Stop!
让我们进去！
Let us in!
我们不会走的！
We're not leaving!
转过来！
Turn!
给我转过来！
Turn it around!
转回来！转回来一点！
Get back! Back!
发射！
Fire!
我看到她了！
I can see her!
准备！
Ready!
推起！
Move!
发射！
Fire!
- 装箭！ - 装箭！
- Reload! - Reload!
快点！
Faster!
再快点！
Hurry!
发射！
Fire!
走起来！
Go!
跑起来！
Run!
女王陛下
Your Grace.
我们所需要的只是致命一击而已
All we need is one good shot.
陛下 所有的蝎弩都被毁了
The scorpions have all been destroyed, Your Grace.
科本
被剥夺项链的学士 瑟曦的女王之手
格雷果·克里冈
“魔山”
铁舰队还把守着黑水湾
The Iron Fleet hold Blackwater Bay.
攸伦杀了她的一条龙
Euron killed one of her dragons.
他也能把另一条干掉
He can kill another.
女王陛下 铁舰队已陷入火海
Your Grace, the Iron Fleet is burning.
城门也全部被突破
The gates have been breached.
还有黄金团——
The Golden Company--
我们的军队会比佣兵打得更卖力
Our men will fight harder than sellswords ever could.
他们会保卫他们的女王 直到最后一个人倒下
They will defend their queen to the last man.
- 是的 女王陛下 - 红堡从未陷落
- Yes, Your Grace. - The Red Keep has never fallen.
今日也绝不会陷落
It won't fall today.
不 不 不要！
No, no, no!
让开 让开！
Move, move!
跑
Run.
跑啊！
Run!
快点！
Come on!
- 敲钟！- 敲钟啊！
- Ring the bells! - Ring the bells!
钟！
The bells!
- 敲钟！- 快敲钟！
- Ring the bells! - Ring the bells!
快他妈敲钟啊！
Ring the bloody bells!
- 敲钟！- 敲钟！
- Ring the bells! - Ring the bells!
让女王敲钟
Tell the queen to ring the bells.
敲钟！敲钟！
Ring the bells! Ring the bell!
走这边
This way.
敲钟！
Ring the bell!
敲响它们！
Ring them!
敲钟！
Ring the bells!
- 敲钟！- 救救我们！
- Ring the bells! - Help us!
以女王之名……
In the name of the--
我们投降了！
Queen! We're surrounded!
- 敲钟！- 快敲啊！
- Ring the bells! - Now! Come on!
赶快！
Hurry up!
敲钟！
Ring the bells!
不！
No!
回来！
Get back!
别动！别动！
Stay! Stay!
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no.
快点 快点
Quickly. Quickly.
停手！
Stop!
- 放开我！放开 婊子！ - 不要 放开！救命！救命！
- Get off me! Get off, bitch! - No, get off! Help! Help!
不要！
No!
走！
Go!
快走！
找个地方躲起来
Find somewhere to hide.
我的天啊！
My God!
弑君者
The Kingslayer.
我们要让女王离开君临
We need to get the queen out of King's Landing.
听听
Listen.
这是城市覆灭的声音
That's the sound of a city dying.
已经完了
It's over.
好吧 对你来说也许是
Well, maybe for you.
如果你在死前杀死了另一位国王
If you kill another king before you die...
他们会永远歌颂你
they'll sing about you forever.
你不是国王
You're no king.
哈 我还就是了
Oh, but I am.
我还操了女王
And I fucked the queen.
如果我赢了……
If I win...
我会把你的脑袋带给瑟曦
I'll bring your head to Cersei
这样你就可以和她吻别了
so you can kiss her one last time.
女王陛下 这里已经不再安全了
Your Grace, it isn't safe here any longer.
红堡是全城最安全的地方
The Red Keep is the safest place in the city.
无垢者已经攻破了红堡的大门
The Unsullied have breached the gates of the Red Keep.
梅葛楼应该更安全
Maegor's Holdfast would be a better place
去那躲躲这场风暴
to wait out the storm.
对一个残废来说……
You fought well...
你还挺能打的
for a cripple.
你又弑了一回君
Another king for you.
但是我也没输！
But I got you!
我也杀了你！
I got you!
我是杀了詹姆·兰尼斯特的人
I'm the man who killed Jaime Lannister.
回家去吧 女孩
Go home, girl.
她要么会被烧死
The fire will get her,
要么被多斯拉克人杀死
or one of the Dothraki.
或者填了龙的肚子
Or maybe that dragon will eat her.
都不重要了 她死定了
It doesn't matter. She's dead.
你要是再不离开这里 你也会死
And you'll be dead too if you don't get out of here.
我要去杀了她
I'm going to kill her.
你以为只有你一个人为复仇等了很久吗？
You think you wanted revenge a long time?
我这辈子都在等这个机会
I've been after it all my life.
我活着只为了这个
It's all I care about.
现在看着我 看着我！
And look at me. Look at me!
你想变成我这个样子吗？
You wanna be like me?
再跟着我 你会死在这
You come with me, you die here.
桑铎
Sandor.
谢谢你
Thank you.
女王陛下
Your Grace.
你好啊 哥哥
Hello, big brother.
格雷果爵士 呆在我身边
Ser Gregor, stay by my side.
格雷果爵士 我命令你
Ser Gregor, I command you.
服从你的女王 格雷果爵士
Obey your queen, Ser Gregor.
瞧瞧 这才是你
Yeah, that's you.
你一直都是这副丑样子
That's what you've always been.
你受伤了
You're hurt.
没关系
It doesn't matter.
你在流血
You're bleeding.
阿兰娜！
Alanna!
阿兰娜！你有见到我老婆吗？
Alanna! Have you seen my wife?
你有看到我老婆吗？
Have you seen my wife?
闪开！
Out of the way!
不！
No!
唔
Oh.
拉住我
Take my hand.
拉住我的手
站起来 站起来
Get up. Get up.
- 不 不 - 等等 等一下！
- No. No.- Wait! Wait!
不！
No!
他妈的去死吧！
Fucking die!
我们需要撤退！
We need to fall back!
撤到城墙外面去！
Fall back behind the wall!
- 撤退！- 撤退！
- Fall back!- Fall back!
撤到城外！
Get out of the city!
撤退！
Fall back!
- 撤退！- 快撤！
- Fall back!- Fall back!
你们不能呆在这里
You can't stay here.
你们要不停地逃
You have to keep moving.
我们不能出去
We can't go out there.
你们必须要出去
You have to.
在外边的人都死了
Everyone out there is dead.
如果你们都躲在这里 也都会死
If you stay here, you'll die.
跟着我
Follow me.
都跟上！
Follow me!
过来 快点 跟我来
Come on, quickly. Come to me.
把他扶起来
Lean him up there.
所有人 动作快！
Come on, quickly. All of you!
快跑！
Run!
跑！
妈妈！
Mama!
妈妈！不
Mama! No.
妈妈！妈妈！
Mama! Mama!
妈妈！
Mama!
起来
Get up.
快起来！
Get up!
我们得赶紧离开
We have to keep moving.
带她走
Take her.
带她走！
Take her!
- 带她走 - 快来！
- Take her.- Come on!
快来！
Come on!
往这边走
This way.
我想让我们的孩子活下去
I want our baby to live.
别让我死掉 詹姆 求你别让我死掉
Don't let me die, Jaime.Please don't let me die.
没关系
It's all right.
- 求你别让我死掉 - 没关系
- Please don't let me die.- It's all right.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
你看——你看着我
Just look-- Look at me.
- 看着我 - 我不要这样死去
- Look at me.- Not like this.
我不要这样死去 不要这样
Not like this. Not like this.
你看——你看着——看着我的眼睛
Look-- Look-- Look me in the eye.
别转移视线 别看其他——
Don't look away. Don't look--
看着我！你看着我就好
Look at me! Just look at me.
什么都不重要了
Nothing else matters.
只要我们还在一起
Only us.
衣柜字幕组出品
冰火中文维基：http://asoiaf.huijiwiki.com/
本集关键字：红堡 魔山 疯王
《权力的游戏》下集预告